{
    "id": "b278119db50e4f5ca6f5ca7da59f8813",
    "title": "Other vs. Another",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Can I have .................................. cup of coffee?",
            "description": "Another means additional or extra.",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "36822a3e7f3e45628c505b3d2c1cda4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "They looked at each ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "others",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26d577ff0b2740dfa412de0c85dc0911"
        },
        {
            "question": "You take this and I will take the ......................................... one.",
            "description": "Other means one that is different or distinct from one that has already been mentioned.",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "others"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7ddc8aa9b3404b9faa934aeb32eb9df7"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must love one .............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "99bfea652c4c4c9c96d8e26f0116cb5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ...................................... people have arrived.",
            "description": "Other means one that is different or distinct from one that has already been mentioned.",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "others"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afd659b91b154d908f43efdb4ad8ccc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many .......................................... have also come.",
            "description": "We use the plural form others after many.",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "others",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3bc6d7ea33e345f18506996792d46dba"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will never get ........................................... chance.",
            "description": "Another means additional or extra.",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "others",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a2279a7af9524a1d9e03cc16c89a2590"
        },
        {
            "question": "One man's meat is ........................................ man's poison.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "others",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2b1ab6ef381a4af98698740258437a51"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw her ........................................ day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "the other"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc58295fa11c4c0aa9f786868fc31cf3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the .................................... woman?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "others",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f081bc3ff3b41e3a5f0a68fbfc3fa8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will take the …………………………. shirt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10654903a35542599d63e9fe73eebc09"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have bought ………………………… flat in Dubai.",
            "description": "Another means an extra.",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5cdeb5f22fe24986ac36d00b45dfa689"
        }
    ]
}